{
    "subject": "resource/SageTV",
    "predicate": "property/location",
    "object": "resource/Inglewood,_California",
    "human_readable": "SageTV is located in Inglewood, California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9590919017791748,
            "question": "Is SageTV located in California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8891626000404358,
            "question": "Where is SageTV located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.842639684677124,
            "question": "In what state is SageTV located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8265302181243896,
            "question": "What is the location of SageTV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7139814496040344,
            "question": "Where can you find SageTV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6955625414848328,
            "question": "In which US state is SageTV situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6141580939292908,
            "question": "What city is the home of SageTV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.522436797618866,
            "question": "Can you tell me the city of SageTV's headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5009132623672485,
            "question": "What is the address of SageTV's headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4652426540851593,
            "question": "If you were to visit SageTV, what city would you go to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=SageTV is located in Inglewood, California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3248_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the address of SageTV's headquarters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3248_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me the city of SageTV's headquarters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3248_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city is the home of SageTV?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3248_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3248_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3248_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3248_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3248_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3248_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3248_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3248_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3248_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3248_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3248_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to multiple documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3248/re-ranker-msmarco/6.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3248/re-ranker-msmarco/24.txt, and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3248/re-ranker-msmarco/61.txt), SageTV is indeed located in Inglewood, California."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents explicitly state that \"SageTV is located in Inglewood, United States.\" While the specific mention of California might not be present, Inglewood is a city in Los Angeles County, California. Therefore, the statement that SageTV is located in Inglewood, California, can be considered correct based on this information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}